export const chapter = "Chapter - 10: Adverb";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "What type of adverb shows the manner in which an action is done?",
          optionA: "Adverbs of Time",
          optionB: "Adverbs of Place",
          optionC: "Adverbs of Manner",
          correctAnswer: "Adverbs of Manner",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which adverb type indicates the place where an action is done?",
          optionA: "Adverbs of Degree or Quantity",
          optionB: "Adverbs of Place",
          optionC: "Interrogative Adverbs",
          correctAnswer: "Adverbs of Place",
        },
        {
          question: "What do adverbs of frequency indicate?",
          optionA: "How often an action is done",
          optionB: "The manner in which an action is done",
          optionC: "The place where an action is done",
          correctAnswer: "How often an action is done",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which adverb is used to ask questions like where, why, when, and how?",
          optionA: "Interrogative Adverbs",
          optionB: "Adverbs of Time",
          optionC: "Adverbs of Degree or Quantity",
          correctAnswer: "Interrogative Adverbs",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the sentence 'He did the job best of all,' which degree of adverb is used?",
          optionA: "Positive",
          optionB: "Comparative",
          optionC: "Superlative",
          correctAnswer: "Superlative",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Where should an adverb be placed to modify a transitive verb according to the given rules?",
          optionA: "At the beginning of a sentence",
          optionB: "In the mid-position, between subject and verb",
          optionC: "After the direct object",
          correctAnswer: "After the direct object",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is the general rule for the position of adverbs of degree?",
          optionA: "End-position",
          optionB: "Mid-position",
          optionC: "Both end-position and mid-position",
          correctAnswer: "Both end-position and mid-position",
        },
        {
          question:
            "When does an adverb of definite frequency generally appear in a sentence?",
          optionA: "Mid-position",
          optionB: "End-position",
          optionC: "Initial-position",
          correctAnswer: "End-position",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which adverbs are generally placed before the words they modify?",
          optionA: "Adverbs of Place",
          optionB: "Adverbs of Frequency",
          optionC: "Adverbs like even, only, merely, not, never",
          correctAnswer: "Adverbs like even, only, merely, not, never",
        },
        {
          question: "What is the correct position for 'enough' in a sentence?",
          optionA: "Before the word it modifies",
          optionB: "After the direct object",
          optionC: "At the end of a sentence",
          correctAnswer: "Before the word it modifies",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "________ intelligence involves how good a person is at navigating their environment.",
          optionA: "Visual-Spatial",
          optionB: "Linguistic-Verbal",
          optionC: "Logical-Mathematical",
          correctAnswer: "Visual-Spatial",
        },
        {
          question:
            "People with high ______ intelligence tend to be writers, readers, and good at memorizing.",
          optionA: "Visual-Spatial",
          optionB: "Linguistic-Verbal",
          optionC: "Logical-Mathematical",
          correctAnswer: "Linguistic-Verbal",
        },
        {
          question:
            "______ intelligence is concerned with number perception and logical problem-solving.",
          optionA: "Visual-Spatial",
          optionB: "Linguistic-Verbal",
          optionC: "Logical-Mathematical",
          correctAnswer: "Logical-Mathematical",
        },
        {
          question:
            "People with high ______ intelligence have good body awareness and control.",
          optionA: "Bodily-Kinesthetic",
          optionB: "Musical",
          optionC: "Interpersonal",
          correctAnswer: "Bodily-Kinesthetic",
        },
        {
          question:
            "______ intelligence involves the ability to perceive and transform sound and musical patterns.",
          optionA: "Bodily-Kinesthetic",
          optionB: "Musical",
          optionC: "Interpersonal",
          correctAnswer: "Musical",
        },
        {
          question:
            "People with high ______ intelligence excel at group work and maintaining peace in organizations.",
          optionA: "Bodily-Kinesthetic",
          optionB: "Musical",
          optionC: "Interpersonal",
          correctAnswer: "Interpersonal",
        },
        {
          question:
            "______ intelligence deals with self-awareness and understanding one's own mental-emotional state.",
          optionA: "Intrapersonal",
          optionB: "Naturalistic",
          optionC: "Pedagogical",
          correctAnswer: "Intrapersonal",
        },
        {
          question:
            "______ intelligence involves identifying, classifying, and manipulating elements of the environment.",
          optionA: "Intrapersonal",
          optionB: "Naturalistic",
          optionC: "Pedagogical",
          correctAnswer: "Naturalistic",
        },
        {
          question:
            "People with high ______ intelligence tend to understand a topic and help others understand it.",
          optionA: "Intrapersonal",
          optionB: "Naturalistic",
          optionC: "Pedagogical",
          correctAnswer: "Pedagogical",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Artificial intelligence aims to stimulate human attributes of these nine intelligences but has been most successful in achieving ______ intelligence.",
          optionA: "Intrapersonal",
          optionB: "Naturalistic",
          optionC: "Logical-Mathematical",
          correctAnswer: "Logical-Mathematical",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "Adverbs of Manner describe the place where an action is done.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Adverbs of Time indicate how often an action is done.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Adverbs of Place modify verbs, adjectives, or other adverbs.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Adverbs of Degree or Quantity show the quantity or extent of an action.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Interrogative Adverbs are used to express doubt or uncertainty.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Relative Adverbs refer back to their antecedents.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Intrapersonal intelligence involves understanding one's own mental-emotional state.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Naturalistic intelligence is concerned with number perception and logical problem-solving.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Pedagogical intelligence involves identifying, classifying, and manipulating elements of the environment.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Artificial intelligence has been most successful in achieving Interpersonal intelligence.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
